Roaming the street's...
end and lane's edge,
yet never yielding.
Peddling dope...
and drugs,
yet always brotherhood shielding.
After the turmoil,
of killings,
bloodbaths,
loss,
and pain,
Ba in order to protect his friends,
Ba gave his life
in the battle at The North Port.
Hai Cuong ended up in jail,
facing the consequences of his actions.
Using his abilities,
Hao has led Chinatown
to function more expertly each day.
He has created
multiple flourishing front businesses.
Long and Phong have
become his powerful right-hand men.
The security situation
is more unstable than ever.
Hung's leadership in the battle against
crime has intensified at this phase.
That action has had
a direct impact
on the benefits of a covert group,
forcing them to free
the tiger back into the woods.
They are considered to be the Council,
a group that manipulates
the underworld's hierarchy.
Chinatown is more unstable than ever.
BROTHERS FOR LIFE 3
[Episode 3: Fate's Decree]
Open the door for him.
Who are you looking for?
Who is it, Dung?
Hello, mom.
I'm Long's friend.
He invited me here for dinner.
Dung, help me get up.
Here's your water.
You should call Long.
Tell him to
come home soon for dinner.
I'm listening.
Have you invited
anyone to our house?
Tell him that A Din is here.
Do you have shoulder pain?
I used to study a bit...
of traditional medicine.
Let me help you.
Long, is that you?
I'll go to the kitchen
and prepare dinner for you.
Next time, don't come home this late.
Don't let your mom and wife
wait for you.
Dung,
take mom downstairs to get her stuff.
About Chinatown's situation,
if I were you,
I would give it up right away.
A wise man
shapes himself to the circumstances.
Am I right, mom?
Take mom downstairs now.
What have you done to Hao?
I helped him
meet his ancestors a little earlier.
You…
What did you just say?
I killed Hao, mom.
Killed?
You...
Mom?
Mom, open your eyes!
Please open your eyes!
Call an ambulance for her.
Mom?
- Get the old woman to the hospital.
- Mom!
Call an ambulance
to the nearest hospital.
Mom?
How is your mom?
Merely stable now.
Where are you going?
I'm going to talk to Din.
Are you out of your mind?
What the fuck
are you going to talk about?
Be careful or you'll be
the next one on deathbed.
What?
Look what he did to Long's mom.
How could I sit here after that?
Aren't you a police officer?
Why don't you arrest him?
Arrest him?
You really think it's that simple?
Do you want me to arrest him
for going to someone
else's house to peel fruit?
Get some sense, Phong.
If you won't
fucking do it, I will.
Listen.
I will take revenge
more unstable than ever.
Phong, I beg you to
cease causing any trouble, please.
Do you have any plans?
Huh?
Tell me.
After gathering all the brothers,
what are you going to do to him?
Remember that they all have families.
If something were to happen,
nobody would take care of their families.
Can you handle that?
What a bummer.
We are gangsters,
not philosophers.
What is your plan, then?
[Transfer Contract]
Holy shit.
Boss,
the iron parcel has arrived.
This is from Mr. Sau.
Bring the case back to him.
Chinatown is under my control.
Double the batch next time.
Hey.
Take this away as well.
Leaving it here could blow me up.
Put it down here.
I need your place.
Do you have a problem?
Long.
Dung.
What's the matter?
There have been deaths in our area.
What was the reason?
Drugs.
What?
Rules are rules.
Drug dealing is prohibited.
I'm simply making money.
Why must you
make things hard for me?
You're taking
Din's side now, aren't you?
Damn you!
That asshole murdered Hao!
Do you have the courage to oppose him?
We've lost too many people.
I'm unable to
take care of their families.
If everyone disobeys
the rules out of fear for Din,
you are putting
your children and family at risk
and could end up behind bars.
I am in dire need
of everyone's unified strength
for the sake of Chinatown.
If anybody is unwilling,
I won't stand in the way.
Brother.
I address you...
as a brother out of respect for you.
Before taking his last breath,
brother Hao entrusted Chinatown to Long.
If you've got a problem,
then get lost!
I've already made up my mind.
The decision is yours to consider.
What an asshole.
What's the plan, Long?
Nearly ninety percent
of our area has been taken.
Everyone must not act recklessly.
For now,
keep an eye on
where they're transporting the drugs to.
Then I'll get Hung
to deplete their resources.
How then can
we carry on with our business?
I'm listening.
This approach is the only way for the
authorities to handle Din effectively.
Hello?
You should not call me at times like this.
At times like this,
it is most fitting.
Din has cooperated with Sau Mui.
What?
A huge drugs shipment is arriving.
Do not let your juniors ruin everything.
I see.
We started off
saying we'd make cash together.
Yet now,
all of our business
establishments are closed.
No deals going down.
There's nothing we can do.
What did you promise us at first?
You were bursting with confidence,
weren't you?
Put in here.
Sweet dreams, gatekeeper.
Let's go!
Hurry, hurry!
Quick!
Move aside! Move aside!
Let's fill the tank completely.
You dare think sitting here with me
makes you my equal, huh?
I'm...
only doing business for profit.
I don't want any trouble.
About Chinatown,
we will wait
until you have complete control.
When giants quarrel,
the dwarfs like us get squashed.
Boss, come here!
- What?
- Help me! Help me!
To the right.
- Is it done?
- Is it okay, boss?
Taste this.
- Boss! Boss!
- What?
Fuck!
Boss.
Everywhere!
Let them have a big buffet today.
We have plenty of shits.
Have a full meal, suckers.
- Go, go.
- Retreat. Retreat.
Go, go.
Wait a second.
So stinky!
Go find out who did this!
Yes sir!
Yeah! Yeah!
- Yeah yeah!
Wait, wait, wait.
Let me call Long.
Where my phone?
Mom, drink some milk
after you eat the porridge to feel better.
I'm listening, what's up?
Long.
I've got a really
hilarious story to tell you in a bit.
Talk to you later, okay?
Okay. Okay.
- Yeah, yeah!
What kind of driving is that?
You're having too much fun, little kid.
Careful!
Idiot!
Wait, wait, wait.
I need to brag to Hung.
Hello?
Hung!
I've got a really
hilarious story to tell you in a bit.
Oh. Okay.
Was it Phong again?
Yeah.
He called
to ask about mom's health.
Are you hiding anything from me?
Actually…
I'm handling a few matters.
After everything is done,
I will take you and mom back home.
Okay?
You must be careful.
You're the only one I have now.
You know that, don't you?
I know.
I'll come in with mom.
Okay...
I am not strong enough
to continue living like Ut Det.
Bring this back to Mr. Sau.
Remember to collect
all the goods for me next month.
How is the task I assigned you?
It's done.
Bastards.
Are you up for playing foul?
What are you doing, Long?
You have a family to take care of.
Think of your mother,
your wife.
Remove yourself from this mess.
We didn't do it on purpose.
We simply thought
we could help you achieve something
to solve the case. That's all.
What do you know
about police procedures?
Such actions
only stir up the wasp's nest.
When will we ever discover their source?
When will Chinatown
finally achieve peace?
Hey!
Dumbass.
My hands are full of shits.
Hey.
My heads are full of shits.
Hey,
I wish you guys
could witness that scene.
Damn.
This time I made them eat shit literally.
Not just a piece.
A whole tank.
Too bad you guys weren't there.
It would've been
even more fun if you were there.
Are you using me
to take revenge on Din?
What?
Am I your henchman?
Nobody thinks of you like that.
It was just
killing two birds with one stone.
Relax.
Why are you so tense?
How silly!
Listen to me.
You have to use your imagination.
I'm standing here...
and I can still smell the shit over there.
Cheers!
I don't want to hear
any more of your shitty story.
So…
What about
stories involving drugs?
Do you want to hear?
I do know something.
I assume
it might be important to you.
Do you want to know?
Hear him out.
You won't regret it.
A huge drugs shipment is going to arrive…
Do you really believe what they said?
Yes.
They might not think things over,
but they've never been dishonest with me.
Don't you think...
they're taking advantage of you,
using you to eradicate one another?
Look at yourself.
Have you spent
so much time as a gangster
that you've forgotten who you are?
Take some time off for now.
Dad!
I cannot withdraw
from the investigation at this time.
Comrade Hung!
We can't kick off a mission
over a single sentence.
They've never been dishonest with you.
I understand, but…
I'm only saying
you should rest for a while.
Or do you want to be
eliminated from the investigation team?
Roger that!
Damn, the truck is cramped already.
Whose stinky fart is that?
Mine.
Boss?
Dumbass! Dumbass!
Boss.
- What?
- I have an idea.
Could you change to
a more spacious truck someday?
This one is too cramped,
I can barely breath.
Only if you
cleaned all the shit of this city.
Focus on your job.
Could it be that
I have to do this until old age?
What a bright future.
Do you know Ding Lik?
Who is that?
He cleaned shit...
and became the boss
of the Bund of Shanghai.
Amazing, huh?
How cool!
Of course.
Be optimistic.
Be optimistic! Be optimistic!
Be optimistic!
Be bright!
Optimistic! Optimistic!
Go, go, go!
Who took the deal this morning?
It was me.
I cannot contact them.
Have you checked the location carefully?
It's him.
He gave directions this morning.
Screw you!
Brother Long!
Run!
This way, brother Long!
Even a cleaning service
got canceled last minute.
Look, boss.
It's a truck that looks like ours.
I see.
They definitely
got canceled last minute just like us.
Hey,
fellow workmate.
Got canceled last minute?
Fuck! Kill them all!
You bastards! Come here!
Fuck.
Boss.
Although we
weren't born on the same day...
Worst case scenario, we shall die.
Brothers for life!
Run!
They will have you killed!
This way.
Mom...
BROTHERS FOR LIFE 3